Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Publications Collection, 1904-2015
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Publications Collection, 1904-2015
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Publications Collection, 1904-2015
24-4-3390
1 cubic ft.
College publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Publications of the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Publications of the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine.
Subjects:
Veterinary medicine -- Study and Teaching; Veterinarians.; Veterinary colleges.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Christmas Letters, 1908-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1-7)
  Many of these letters are available online here: http://ecommons.cornell.edu/handle/1813/45066
- Honor Day Programs, 1936-2003 (Box 1, Folder 8-13)
- Annual Conference Programs, 1909-2004 (Box 1, Folder 14-25)
- Annual Conference Programs for Spouses, 1971-1990 (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
- Annual Conference Programs of Clinics and Demonstrations, 1933-1955 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Annual Conference Abstracts, 1953, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 29-30)
- Society of Comparative Medicine - Banquet Programs, 1904, 1905, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Poultry Disease School Program, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Conference on Public Health for Veterinarians, 1956, 1959, 1961, 1964, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Open House Programs, 1969, 1977, 1980, 1983, 1985, 2002, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Ruminant Health-Nutrition Conference Program, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- James Law Lecture Series Program, 1980-1995 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Animal Pain and Its Control Program, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Farrier's Conference, 1993, 1994, 1996, 1998, 2001, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- International Symposium on Bovine Viral Diarrhea Virus, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Fred Scott Feline Symposium, 1997-1999, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- International Equine Neurology Conference, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Veterinary Laser Surgery for the Small Animal Practice, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Equine Practitioners Conference, 2001, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Cornell Symposium for Dog Enthusiasts, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Student Information Booklet, 1952-1979 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Clinic and Lab Brochures - Equine, Small Animal,Endoscopy Lab, Various Hospitals for Animals, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Veterinary College Brochures, 1963-2002 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Building Dedication Brochures, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- "Don't Forget the Horse Doctor" Booklet, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Vet School Highlights, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- "The Horse" Booklet, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Bovine Research Center, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Catalogs, 1992-1993; 1997-1998; 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- "A Centennial Celebration", 1994 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Report of Private Support, 1997, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Cancer Pets and People Brochure, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Robert S. Hatfield Fellow in Economic Education Program, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Black Tie and Tails Benefit, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- "All Features Great and Small" - Student Chapter of the AVMA, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  Spring
- Veterinary Dermatology Conference Program and Biological and Biomedical Sciences Symposium Program, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Statler Club Menus - Vet College Featured, 1965, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Equine Research Report, no date (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Facilities Master Plan Booklet, no date (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Poster Abstracts - Comparative Aspects of Physiology of Digestion in Ruminants - Satellite Meeting of the XXX International Congress of the International Union of Physiological Sciences, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Second Annual Cornell Equine Conference, 1972-11-16-1972-11-18 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Diagnostic Laboratory Dedication, 1978-10-17 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Veterinary Diagnostic Laboratory User's Guide, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Report of the Commissioner's Task Force for the Veterinary Diagnositc Services for New York State, 2001-06 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  Planning for our Future